JESSICA CLAIRE

- resumesample@example
- (555) 432-1000,
- Montgomery Street, San Francisco, CA 94105

- **?**:
- A
- 8
- 6

SUMMARY

Manager with 12 years of background in customer service, finance, leadership and branch management. Vast knowledge of finance, regulatory requirements and general bank operations. Enthusiastic and energetic in leading staff to exceed sales goals, while delivering excellent customer service. A dedicated team player experienced in overseeing operations of individual and multi-unit facilities, developing successful programs to improve profitability. Diligent and driven individual who has achieved success in a variety of roles with increasing levels of responsibility. An effective communicator and team-builder with strong analytical, management and organizational skills.

EDUCATION

Strayer University Charlotte, NC • 2015 – –

BBA: Banking - GPA:

Holly Hill Roberts High School Holly Hill, SC • 1999 – –

High School Diploma: College Preparatory -GPA:

EXPERIENCE

Bluegreen Resorts - Branch Banking Coordinator

Hershey, PA, · · 03/2013 - Current

- · Supervise and participate in daily operational functions of the branch's Teller area
- Ensure timely and efficient completion of client transactions
- Proactively manage the daily sales/quality referral process
- Assist HR with recruiting, interviewing, and selecting oncoming associates
- Research Out of Balance Transactions/Daily Reports/Completed corrections in a timely manner, with daily Vault Operations/Cash Master
- Assist with Risk Management practices while being responsible for staffing and scheduling of branch
- Complete Staff Development/Performance Reviews/Salary Administration Ensure operating procedures are followed as outlined in the Branch Operational Manual (BOM).

First Busey Corporation - Guest Service Agent

Port Charlotte, FL, • • 03/2012 - 05/2015

- Greets, registers, and assigns rooms to guests, while maintaining confidential information as it relates to guest records.
- · Promptly and effectively deals with guest requests and complaints.
- Answers and routes calls as appropriate; takes guest messages with accuracy.
- Responsible for cash drawer contents, transactions during shift, and night drops as necessary.
- Maintains accurate records including cash flows, registration cards, reservation cards, and property walks.
- Answers inquiries pertaining to hotel services, registration of guests, and travel directions.Â
- · Preferred experience OnQ Software.

Wells Fargo - Service Manager II

City, STATE, • • 06/2007 - 01/2012

- Ensure policies, procedures and security guidelines are followed Educate customers on products, services and alternative solutions.
- Maintained compliance of vault, deposit logs, & risk mitigation Conducted on the spot coaching to ensure tellers convey quality customer service.
- · Exhibited effective leadership skills in motivating teams to meet company goals.
- Assisted in Hiring, Terminating, Training Created/Maintained/Delivered
 Performance Evaluations of Employees Performed initial Audits/Reports randomly
 on a monthly basis.

Hampton Inn - Manager/Auditor

City, STATE, • • 02/2004 - 06/2007

- Processed guest payments for room charges, food and beverage charges and phone charges.
- Greeted and registered guests and issued room keys.
- Delivered requested items to guests' rooms.
- Processed credit card transactions during the checkout process.
- Supervised front desk staff.
- Monitored the appearance and performance of the front desk staff.
- Fostered strong working relationships with all hotel departments.
- Performed bookkeeping activities, such as balancing accounts and conducting nightly audits.
- Recorded guest comments or complaints, referring customers to managers as necessary.
- Directed personnel, training and labor relations activities.
- Served as a link between management and employees by handling questions, interpreting and administering contracts and helping resolve work-related problems.

SKILLS

Accounting, accounts payable, Accounts Payable and Receivable, auditing, balance sheet, billing, bookkeeping, Budgets, cash receipts, Closing, Coaching, Excellent communication, hardware, Conflict resolution, contracts, Credit, checkout process, client, Customer Relations, excellent customer service, Customer Service, finance, financial, Forecasting, forklifts, Hiring, Human resources management, Human Resource, HR, internal audit, internet connectivity, labor relations, Team building, Leadership Skills, loss prevention, Managing, marketing, money, 97, Operations management, Payroll, Performance Reviews, personnel, Policies, processes, process improvement, quality, quality control, Recruiting, Research, Risk Management, Sales, Scheduling, shipping, Staff Development, staffing, telephone, telephone etiquette, phone, time management, Trainer, warehousing